<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jeff&#39;s Wall of Writing</title>
    <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jeff&#39;s Wall of Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 16:11:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dracula : The Andrei Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/the-andrei-chronicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 16:11:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/the-andrei-chronicles/</guid>
      <description>A loud wailing arose from the castle grounds.
“Spare him, please! Take me instead!”
I raised my head for a moment to acknowledge the despair and resumed my reading.
“Sigh, another one bites the dust,” thinking to myself.
My father must have taken a fresh human baby from nearby Transylvania, and naturally, its mother came chasing after — only to suffer the same fate.
At 4 AM, my father came in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waiting Room</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/waiting-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:54:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/waiting-room/</guid>
      <description>Ten minutes early!
Take a ticket,
Have a seat
Now serving,
Seventy - five!
Twiddle both my thumbs,
Glance from left to right,
How much time passed?
How much more?
Don’t get bored,
Stay sharp, stay sharp,
Breathe in, breathe out, repeat!
Inner restlessness,
it gets to me.
Must stay sharp —
Idleness
makes my eyes to
close hard shut, never
to wake up again.
Struggling to struggle.
Help, help, help me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pickles</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/pickles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:03:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/pickles/</guid>
      <description>TO take from a common saying, when life gives you _________, you make pickles. (The blank must be a type of fruit or vegetable) Relative to lemonade, pickles may be the sweeter choice — that is, in terms of health.
I grew up having a serving of yogurt a day. I thought it was just one of those things your parents tell you to do, and you do it, just like eating your veggies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreamwalkers</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/dreamwalkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:01:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/dreamwalkers/</guid>
      <description>Jordan followed the wolf twins along the exposed riverbed laden with boulders and fallen tree trunks. The moon was bright that night and illuminated their path with surprising clarity. Finally, Seraphine turned around and faced me.
“We are here. Allow us a moment to tell mother about our arrival,” said Seraphine.
They were still along the riverbed, far below the adjacent forest above. On the left side of the riverbed, there lay the entrance to the wolves’ den.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Fearful-Avoidants Do</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/fearful-avoidants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/fearful-avoidants/</guid>
      <description>Joe and Isaiah had been classmates in a math class. Isaiah is a distinguished scholar in mathematics, and Joe really admires his ability. Joe is working on a research project and needs ideas for modeling a particular event. Immediately, Joe thinks of Isaiah and comes up with a way of asking him for help.
Joe: Isaiah might know a thing or two about this. Let me give him a ping and see what he says.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to Holden Caulfield from the Catcher in the Rye</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/letter-to-holden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:19:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/letter-to-holden/</guid>
      <description>The mark of the immature man is that he wants to die nobly for a cause, while the mark of the mature man is that he wants to live humbly for one.
Dear Holden,
I appreciate you for sharing your story, for it gives me hope that there are others who value authenticity and integrity in a world that seems to say otherwise.
Frustrated, angry, disappointed, and lonely — these are the feelings that characterize the last four years of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down the Rabbit Hole</title>
      <link>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/down-the-rabbit-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:09:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffkwang.github.io/posts/down-the-rabbit-hole/</guid>
      <description>Remember what the dormouse said: feed your head
Jeff was beginning to feel very annoyed as he sat by the river. He was reading a book with no beginning nor end. “What is the point of this?” he thought. As he put the book down, he saw a white rabbit run by. It muttered to itself, “I have got no time… no time.” The white rabbit was a peculiar creature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
